const queryList = [
  {
    question: "Who can participate in HackOverflow?",
    answer:
      "HackOverflow welcomes participation from students across a wide range of colleges, offering them the opportunity to compete, collaborate, and showcase their skills alongside peers from diverse educational backgrounds.",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the allowed team size, and can team members be from different colleges?",
    answer:
      "The team size can range from a minimum of 3 to a maximum of 6 members, and participants can form teams with members from different colleges.",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the schedule for HackOverflow?",
    answer:
      "The last date for registration is October 11, 2024. The hackathon will take place on the 18th and 19th of October 2024.",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the total prize pool?",
    answer: `The total prize pool for HackOverflow is ₹30,000, which will be split as follows:
• 1st Place: ₹15,000
• 2nd Place: ₹10,000
• 3rd Place: ₹5,000
`,
  },
  {
    question: "Is accommodation provided for participants?",
    answer:
      "Participants traveling from distant locations will be provided with accommodation for added convenience. This accommodation will be available for one night, specifically the day before the hackathon, ensuring they are well-rested and prepared for the event.",
  },
  {
    question: "What are the travel options near the venue?",
    answer:
      "Participants have the option to travel by either train or bus. The closest transportation hubs are Bhimavaram Town Railway Station and Bhimavaram Bus Stand, both conveniently located for easy access to the hackathon venue.",
  },
  {
    question: "Will there be certificates for participation?",
    answer: `
   All participants will receive certificates of participation, which will be sent to them via email, recognizing their involvement and contribution to the HackOverflow event.
    `,
  },
  {
    question: "Can teams change their members after registration?",
    answer:
      "No, teams cannot change their members after registration.",
  },
  {
    question: "What are the communication channels for participants to reach out to the organizing team?",
    answer: `
Participants can reach out for any inquiries via email at srkrcodingclub@gmail.com. Alternatively, they can contact us directly by phone:
- Avinash (Tech Lead): +91 9346729461
- Jagadeesh (Tech Lead): +91 8919317202
- Tarun (Tech Team Representative): +91 9959132169

Feel free to reach out, and we're here to help you with any questions or concerns you might have.
`,
  },
  {
    question:"Are there social media or online platforms where participants can follow event updates?",
    answer:"Yes, you can follow our Instagram handle for event updates: https://www.instagram.com/srkr_coding_club?igsh=MTVycDY4cGs3d3I0ZA==",
  },
  {
    question:"Will there be any hardware available for participants to use during the hackathon?",
    answer:"Yes, computers will be available for participants to use during the hackathon. However, participants are strongly encouraged and advised to bring their own equipment to the venue to ensure a smoother, more personalized experience and to avoid any potential mishaps or technical issues during the event.",
  },
  {
    question:"Will there be internet access during the event?",
    answer:"Yes, there will be internet access available during the event to ensure that participants can work efficiently and access any online resources they may need.",
  },
];

export default queryList;
